what's up guys welcome back to another
set and forget uh episode in the podcast
so you guys can tell i got the man
swaggy c here the amount of times that i
have gotten like this in the dms in the
comments has been crazy i'm like bro i'm
not gonna do nothing basic i'm not gonna
you know just do it through zoom you
know it's glitching i'm like bro i will
literally fly out to swagger's house so
first of all before we get into anything
like we've been talking you know we've
been chopping it up for like you know
two three hours already like you know he
gives around the whole entire dorado
this man is about to drop gems like
you've been talking now and i'm just
like i'm gonna stop talking to you i'm
not gonna ask you any more questions i'm
gonna sit here for the podcast so um
first of all i appreciate you bro you
know having me you know come out here to
uh you know your career back here in
puerto rico congratulations appreciate
it like i don't think you guys
understand like not not just the house
itself is an accomplishment this this is
huge but like where you are like this
guy has been showing me around the whole
entire community and it's it's a
different vibe that you don't even feel
that you're in
uh i don't want to say like
a state you're like in your own private
world
nobody's coming with you so i want to
say thank you bro for bringing me out
here congratulations
i told you i was going to be a girl and
uh appreciate you because this is the
first time you're in another podcast
yeah this is my first time ever and all
my you know my audience knows this is
the first time i've ever done a podcast
on somebody else's channel so yeah it's
gonna be a good one so i appreciate it
bro no problem bro
so so let's start off with
real quick
like dorado puerto rico like bro what
why
what the [__]
bro the crazy part about it is that like
nobody knew about this you said this
when we were driving on the golf carts
that like you just moved here i didn't
talk about it for months i didn't talk
about it for years i just moved here
yeah and i've been looking at it for
about a year and a half logan paul put
me on to it and once i realized how much
money i'd save in taxes out here like
we're day traders it's zero percent it's
not 10 it's not 20. it's not 30. like
california was charging me
between 50 and 60 it's zero okay i know
i'm gonna save a lot of money on taxes
and businesses out here and it's
beautiful and it's isolated i don't
believe party like that i like being my
like quiet and peaceful it was a
no-brainer for me i'm not in like these
clubs or anything like that i got a wife
i got a daughter on the way i'll be
chilling so when i came out here and i
moved out here it was like when i made
my video my tour i was like yo what like
how did puerto rico happen yeah i've
grown and matured to the point where
like i don't need to talk about my moves
before i make them whereas in 2020
people know i was talking about
everything so i don't know it just
happened yeah i was telling you because
you know you were telling me like you
know you go chill with jake with logan
and like you you came a couple times
before you actually got the [__] like
you know you toured you know puerto rico
and i'm just like bro why didn't you
make you know content why didn't you
just like post about it or like come bro
nothing you just popped off but you just
got the crib like yeah if logan never
made his video and i never talked to
jake at was the basketball court or at
my gym unbreakable in uh los angeles i
would have never moved here you know and
especially jake's trainer d cut he put
me on so heavily and put me on to the
neighborhood introduced me to so many
people and it was i don't know it's just
an amazing thing but as far as content
people don't know i've been running the
this youtube game for three four years
now i'm i'm
there's not much more i could do
realistically like i've done all the
trading videos you can think of i've
done secure the swag the tv shows i've
done everything you could think of and
now i'm at a point to where like i said
you mentioned on your last podcast we
did it by yourself where i'm going to
give you all content for a full year
then i want to live my life and um
flight 23 he's like flight reacts like a
funny guy who reacts to like nba games
he's like i don't watch the games in
real time because i have a life i just i
just react to them so for me it's like
i've been doing this for 3-4 years now i
just want to live my life with my wife
and my daughter on the way and chill i
still want to interact with my community
do my businesses and love y'all but if
i'm not giving y'all
four videos a week like i used to do two
years ago don't kill me i've done a lot
already you're just living life now yeah
i'm chilling man no trust me you're
living life out here
what's up guys so i've been getting a
ton of questions what broker i'm using
so you guys know i'm a swing trader i
like holding trades for kind of you know
days weeks at a time there's a lot of
pros and cons one of the cons is that
you know you get charged commissions so
i've actually found a broker that has
zero commissions raw spreads uct
withdrawal a bunch of more cool features
you guys can ask me about it so i
finally found the broker if you guys
want to find out more about the broker
the link is in the description below and
let's uh continue with the video i'm
telling you this guy's driving around
the rod i'm like bro like dude i would
have never expected this you get me like
it's i like i even right now like still
being here like being around the
community i've never seen nothing like
this like you know i've i've you know
toured around a little bit like uh like
you know mexico
you know puerto rico dr cuba and it's
just not this like this feels so
exclusive yeah like it's crazy bro so
talking about you know bringing it back
a little bit um
bro where does swaggy start like where
are you i mean originally from because
you said you've never been on a podcast
right so i wanna i want people like give
people like like day one before forex
before basketball tv show bailey
everything like talk to me from day one
yeah so i i grew up i was born in
bridgeport connecticut which is about
you know 20-30 minutes from uh new york
so basically new york is like my my
first home basically um
and then growing up we grew up very very
poor you know my mom and dad got
divorced really really young and i live
with my dad my brother and we were like
homeless like we moved from connecticut
to north carolina and i went to
17 different schools in eight years 17
17 schools in eight years like first
first grade i was in connecticut second
grade connecticut north carolina third
grade north carolina connecticut north
carolina all in the same year like i
mean like
october or august to like october north
carolina october to february january
then i just kept transferring like
because my dad would get a new job or he
had like kidney uh issues so like he'd
be like higher on the list to get a
kidney in connecticut north carolina and
then get higher north carolina
connecticut so we kept switching back
and forth so 17 and eight different
years and we were homeless we were a
point we were sleeping in cars something
shelters for i mean like
at nine years no at six years old and at
13 years old but 13 is when it hit me
the most because when you're about to go
to high school and all your friends are
staying after for this or that you get
off the bus and people are walking to
their homes and like me and my brother
are walking to the local shelter that
scarred me to the point where i said i
never want to want to go through this
again and that's what started my journey
in terms of
financial independence and freedom where
i just wanted to just make as much money
as i possibly could so that me or my
family never had to struggle again
that's kind of where i started where it
was it was you know connecticut and then
that foundation got me to here that's
why i'm such an advocate for financial
literacy whether it's credit mortgage
doesn't got to be forex there's
something wrong with finances because
they don't teach in the school so that's
why i'm so passionate about it that's
crazy i didn't know you were homeless
yeah twice damn twice yeah 17 i remember
it though like it wasn't like i was
homeless at two i remember sleeping in
cars having a little dvd player we
actually used to watch buffy the vampire
slayer and two and a half men there's
the only two things we could watch i
remember watching it and then in the
shelter i remember at the shelter you
know can't believe it by t-pain a little
wayne when it came out i was in the
shelter when i came out lil wayne
lollipop i was in the shelter i remember
watching it at the little
the little living room they had on a
little small i remember watching and
listening to the lyrics i remember all
of that you know what i mean and it
wasn't like i was two years old i don't
remember so that's what you know wrote
me here today and then after that you
told me so you you went to college yeah
you played college but yeah so how did
that how did you transition from college
ball to forex trader entrepreneur yeah
so when when i uh i played college ball
in boston then transferred from boston
to new jersey st peters you know st
peterson went to the elite eight we made
history this year shout out to my boys i
played there and
my first year i was just like basically
red shirt and but the second year when i
was like there i wasn't playing so it
kind of threw me for a loop and then the
third year when i wasn't playing again i
was like okay i got to figure something
else out because the best player on my
team didn't go to the nba he was going
overseas and they weren't really making
that much money okay so i'm just like
okay like
i can
grind as much as i can right now and
then try to go overseas but then what
i'm gonna make 72k a year so i'm a real
big battle rap like advocate i used to
be a part of the community heavily and i
was watching the battle hitman holla
versus sioux surf and before it came on
an ad came on it was tai lopez and tai
lopez said his first hearing my garage
video i remember something in his first
five seconds captivated me to the point
to where i did not click skip the ad i
watched the entire ad
clicked the link for the the seminar
watched the full three hour seminar it
was a health wealth love and happiness
seminar i remember like it was yesterday
and um
this is why you're in college yeah well
i'm in college right right after
practice
i'm gonna be in the cafeteria watching
the ad clicking the link and then going
back to my room to watch the full video
and then
watching it i bought his 67 steps
program and in that program
it wasn't like he mentioned or went into
extensively about 4x but he was talking
about everything you can do stocks forex
options real estate social media
marketing and i researched all of them
and forex was the only one where as a
broke college student was like you can
get in for a hundred dollars and you
don't know what i mean you don't have to
make too much money whereas like stock
market has that pdt rule 25 000 options
just seemed confusing to me and when it
came to forex and real estate i had to
have money for real estate so i was like
okay i'm gonna jump into forex and i
came across baby pips in 2015 and that
well early 2015 like january and that
entire so i was like okay i'm going to
study 4x once school ended from may to
august i sat in my room didn't go out
one time i just studied baby pills from
top to bottom there's a lot of content
there top to bottom bro yeah and then i
bought three different courses went back
to college my last year my junior year
wasn't playing again i was like okay i'm
really gonna figure this forex thing out
and last but not least
march 6 2016 we lost to fairfield in the
first round which was a shocker because
we would rank higher than him we lost if
you go back to my my
second year of trading results video on
youtube
march 10th i made two thousand dollars
my first two thousand dollar date ever
in the market and this was four days you
gotta realize as a basketball player you
wake up you go to you go to a class you
go to practice for three hours you stay
after next year to get shots up you go
to the cafeteria and then it's like nine
ten o'clock at night my first
week where there was no practice like
classes were minimal because the end of
the year yeah i made 2 000. oh no it's
over i'm about to go i'm dropping out
i'm dropping out i
from that moment on i made a plan to
drop out i sent long messages to all my
friends saying i'm not coming back i'm
going to be an entrepreneur a lot of
people i sent the message to left me
already like my coaches girls laughed at
me and said lol good i sent like a
paragraph and they said well good luck
that was it you know what i mean and i
dropped out became a babysitter and then
you know years later i'm here you know
that's right i remember you were a
babysitter you posted some content about
that yeah i couldn't work a nine-to-five
job so babysitting was the only job that
allowed me to make five thousand dollars
a month
while learning how to trade have you
ever had a job other than the
babysitting no i've worked at uh
jcpenney for a week and then i quit oh
[__] like i went through training i sat
in the back for training i was stacking
stuff in the back i quit the next week i
didn't even get my first check i got the
check it was like like a couple of
couple dollars a couple dollars bro you
know what i mean but i didn't get that
and um but before i when i quit there i
applied to be a dishwasher at cheesecake
factory and it told me i was i was
either too qualified or not qualified to
be a dishwasher at that point i was like
i'm never working the job again
babysitting only i could play with kids
being influencing on them and play games
with them while learning how to trade
easy job that's crazy bro so easy let's
tie back to a couple of things so one
tai lopez you said teleport is the one
that kind of motivated you to like you
know get into forex getting uh so nice
because he lives here too that's
that's what i was going to say so how
does it feel like you're like this guy's
neighbor now
i've i've talked to ty several times uh
you you told him and diem and dm not i
never met him uh in person because he's
always traveling to sweden or something
but via dm's i've told him several times
that like i'm only in dorado because of
you even though like i learned from a
forex trader i learned from courses
it started because you laid the
foundation you know what i mean i i
thank you for that you know he's like oh
no problem appreciate it blah blah we
laugh because you know a lot of people
will call him a scam or think he's
something he's out here changing life
like my life would not be what it is if
tai lopez didn't do his hair my garage
video yeah you know so it's like with
the black porsche and the you know you
remember right
of course you know how it is right like
yeah of course yeah so yeah right yeah
so some people may
not like him i'm somebody who likes him
only because he changed my life i don't
like watch his content right right now
because i'm doing what i'm doing right
now but he changed my life so it is kind
of crazy to know that
seven years ago i was watching him and
now i'm living the same neighborhood as
him that's kind of crazy that's that's
that's [__] like that that to me is
like yeah that's just like insane i mean
i'm sure you're gonna bump into him like
once like he kind of comes in and you
know you guys see each other and like i
think that's like where it's going to
kind of hit you so you talked a little
about your journey there how you came
across work so how long did it take for
you to get profitable you know basic
question just just to get that four
years three and a half four years what
happened was i was on a tv show and i
was profitable before the show
but for me it wasn't like grand
profitable it was like four thousand
three thousand five thousand four
thousand six up like it wasn't like
anything crazy
i get on this tv show
um
it's called the challenge
and it's like a real world base and i
get on the tv show and i hated it so
much and it got to the point because i
can't swim right especially that time
yeah and they had us 50 feet over the
water holding on to like a rocket ship
and they were just dropping us plunging
us into the water
and when they plunged me into the water
i couldn't get out i had a life jacket
on but i couldn't get out and i was in
that water for eight minutes while
everybody was laughing it was well
documented on tv and it wasn't until a
guy named kyle
dropped eight minutes after me
and he came up with me grabbed me out of
the water and drug me to the shore and
the minute he did that i went over to
everybody and i told everybody i'm you
will never see me on the show again i
told my wife i'm going to go home i'm
going to figure this thing out to a
point where it's like it's not just one
thousand here then six thousand here
then one thousand and eight no it's
going to be two point words it's a lot
and when i got the show i locked myself
in a cage for
four or five months and then things just
i took like i had a fourteen thousand
um
stipend from the channel so they gave me
14 000 for being on the show how long
were you on the show for
two months no yeah two months i went
there september 20th
no no i went there october and i and i
came back home november 29th so a month
in a month and some change because you
get like i think 3 000 every week you're
on so whatever the weeks is up until 14
i got 14 000. yeah because a lot of
people think you made a [__] ton of
money no no you made nothing big brother
i made uh three thousand dollars from
big brother and that was a show that
captivated everything the challenge paid
me more but i only made 14 000 yeah
there's nothing nothing nothing at all
that's not paying for it that's nothing
at all and then when i came home i had
so many bills that like first of all
like six thousand went away instances
like bills and then in los angeles
but i put like five to six dollars into
an account and i just flipped it to like
60 75 80 90. it got to the point where
it was like 100 and then i was like wow
i really have a huge account right now i
started posting my profits and people
don't remember this what they do
not the people who came across me now
but people who know me for a long time
from that 2019 year
people started seeing all the profits
and i was posting posting and posting
and posting and posting
leading into 2020 posting especially
during the pandemic posting posting
posing consistently the account kept
growing and growing and growing they're
like yo like do you teach yourself i was
like nope i don't teach at all and to
the point where i was like
people kept asking me to teach them so i
was like okay i'm going to make a course
but i never never
and i even told bailey was never in my
life
had an idea that i was going to start a
course that was never the goal the goal
is just to trade and straight to a point
to where i i don't have to be on tv no
more that was my goal i did that but
then it was like oh you can have a
business on this too okay let me start a
course and then i did not think it would
get as big as it did yeah at all because
you're definitely one of like i don't
want to say one of like the pioneers on
youtube but you got in like a covet
everybody was home you know so
everybody's searching how to make money
online yeah i i i made it popular like
the the thing is like people have
different sections when it comes to this
industry like actual fx started the
forex
teaching online type of thing like they
started in 2011
and then q started the
exotic car lifestyle thing
and then i came in during the pandemic
with like a tv show like secure the swag
when it came to uh trading and i made it
popular during the pandemic like so many
people were home and since i had a
natural personality i'm entertaining i
made trading cool like i like when it
came to sean and nat they were like and
they had their suits on but they talked
really slow and they have an accent but
they got good material but they didn't
make it entertaining
q
made uh social media lit with his cards
and stuff but people know cue is not a
talker like that q won't just talk for
five hours straight and two three times
a week for youtube videos i can do that
because i was used to that for tv so i
made it popular um so i am one of the
pioneers but it gets to a point to where
it gets exhausting you know i mean to a
certain extent so you kind of fall back
a little bit but i do love it though
yeah no definitely you're not camera shy
so coming back to the show you met
bailey on the show on the show so how
does having a girl
like supporting your business because
she supports everything yeah for sure
how does that help with your growth
whether it's your business social media
everything like has she helped you out
like does it make a difference yeah i
would not be here if it wasn't for her
because i've made a lot of mistakes and
it was crazy she was the one who pushed
me back into this industry when i got on
tv and i started getting all these
followers even though i wasn't getting
paid i was like yo i'm about to be the
next craziest reality star i'm about to
just
and then after our second show wasn't
making money we even got to argument one
time but she was like yo like when i met
you you were a traitor like like you go
on the cbs show and it says so i can see
day trader like before you was day
trading and that like you seem more
peaceful being on your computer like go
back to that like that that's what's
going to get us out of you know
living regular living normal that's
what's going to get us to this grand
lifestyle not these tv shows
so i needed her especially somebody like
her to push me into back into this
industry but back into
what my goals are because if you have
the wrong woman yes it can tear you down
you have the right woman you will reach
levels you've never reached before and
she's helped me in every single way you
could think of yeah because you've never
at least from what i've seen because you
you're very low key when you're saying
clearly you know you see what we got
going on um but you uh like you're not
really like the party type you don't
really like go out clubbing you don't
really do never i've never never i've
never really partied ever like even i
have friends right now in college who
see me where i am in life and like it
makes sense because every every single
week when we were partying in college
you were studying forex or just doing
your laundry dancing just reading i read
a lot i read a lot i have over a
thousand books like i read a lot i don't
like partying i don't like strip clubs i
don't like none of that because just for
me because of where i
was raised and how i grew up homeless so
i'm like okay my goal is to be a
billionaire that's my goal people may
think that's excessive people may think
it's not going to happen it's going to
happen like i'm telling you like it's
going to especially because i'm hearing
it's going to happen
but it's not going to happen if i'm out
part i do think people need like
relaxing sometimes and to like get away
from all this stuff for me that comes in
fighting i love fighting like i love
sparring yeah like mma like i will go to
thailand for a month and just fight okay
that's it just fight
and
basketball i love that those are my like
releases and fun that's fun for me fun
is not going to a party for me you know
that's why you see i don't have
you know three or four to five different
cars you know what i mean like i just
don't yeah for me that's not fun you
know what i mean for other people who
are car enthusiasts i mean you know who
tj millionaire mentor is
um yeah if you know him he's in los
angeles he loves cars he has like 15
cars and that that's what he loves to do
you know what i mean and just for me i'm
just different you know but no side is
right or both sides are right actually
no side is wrong i mean it's just what
you love to do so you say you say you
want to be a billionaire bro like where
you are right now well what is your goal
to be here because where you are right
now your net bro for me personally like
the business that i've that i've created
the people that i've been surrounding
myself with every single month there's
like a compound interest like my network
just grows right if it's a knowledge
bank account anything it grows right so
like definitely your network is your net
worth so you're i personally think one
of the craziest networking areas that
you could possibly be in by far so
what's your goal like being here other
than you know living your life
peacefully like what's your goal my goal
is for sure to be a billionaire and
people got people got to see that you
got to play like the part that you're in
like this is for example this is the
first time i've put my chains on since
living here like ever like first time
i've lived here for a month and some
changes my first time putting my chains
on because when you're in los angeles
you got a network i realize that when
i'm not
dressed swaggy like or anything like
that people treat you different in the
airport if i'm not wearing my chains i
look regular they would treat me right
they would say oh like you know this is
the first class i will like wait your
turn because i'm just regular when i put
chains on when i put shades on they
treat me like a superstar oh like what's
your name mr oh mr williams like boom we
have to hear you need water and like
they treat you different so you got to
play the part that you're giving when
i'm here
i don't have to play that part when i if
i go to if i'm walking around the
neighborhood i'm wearing chains and i
look like a rapper you push people away
and i'd rather
understand that and play my part i
supposed to be like whoa
they should like me they don't like
doesn't matter what i wear they should
no play the part i'm i'm gonna learn how
to play golf i'm gonna put a suit on i'm
gonna maybe i may wear my chain may not
but i'm gonna put a suit on and play the
parts when they see me then it's like
okay he's clearly in the gates for a
reason he clearly knows what he's doing
then you you are more welcoming so when
i meet these people
then the net worth comes in in terms of
these billion dollar conversations these
multi-million dollar conversations so i
play my part and that's my goal for
being aside from a peaceful life it is
to make a lot of money so that my
great-great-great grandkids can know
that their life is set because i took
the risk where i didn't really party i
didn't really
chase out the girls too much i just
locked in and then my kids can live that
life if they want to yeah because you
just changed your legacy forever bro
like you literally came from being
homeless from new york not like you
could make it out of new york you could
go to let's say i don't know texas we'll
talk a little bit about texas you went
to texas make it out new york you go to
l.a you go to a different city
you went to a different
you live in ireland
you have just changed your legacy like
completely that's the first thing that i
told you like when i came here like i
had a different mindset of kind of like
where i wanted to be obviously i'm a lot
younger how do you know i'm 27 27 i'm
21. yeah i told you yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah you're at a way better spot than i
was at 212. when did you start your
whole journey i started my journey at 19
but i'm saying like 21 i wasn't doing
this like i didn't get to this until
like 23. and i mean at 21 i was still
babysitting and trying to figure out a
way still trading but it was my second
year of trading so i didn't know what
was going it's 2017. yeah i mean so at a
very good spot right now at 21. and i
mean bro like i don't like saying that
age is just a number but like you just
gotta like create same way how you kind
of create like time to read i'm not
really a big reader at least not anymore
because like i wanted you know to learn
reading just a trading every single day
i give myself either like 45 minutes
like an hour and a half where where i
just get my phone and like i put it in a
cabinet and i'll just chill on my
balcony really hard show cause like
where in my building we have a sky
lounge so i'll just chill on the sky
lounge and i'm just like bro let me
think of something and ideas just like
come in like just random crazy things
pop up and like business are created
content is created whatever the case
you're better than me yeah i can't just
sit and think and a business pops up i
have like my every business i've started
or gonna start came from a book and an
idea sparked from it
like you you are very credible just sit
and just sing and something just pops up
i can't do that okay so when you were
locked away you're telling me like your
phone like like you're telling me you're
like you're not going through instagram
no no big brother no you don't have your
phone you don't talk to your family you
don't talk to none of that and now like
now you're telling me you're not going
through the instagram like you you have
no distractions yeah yeah i've i've
muted every single person i follow their
stories their posts i really want to
lock in so
um
i bring the whole team when i go on
instagram i don't see nobody i just see
myself
every single night when i feel like i've
accomplished enough through the day then
yeah i will go through everybody i
follow i click their page not every
single one with the people who inspire
me i really really walk with i'll click
their page see their stories engage
comment other stuff show love but when
i'm working i don't have time to be on
my phone getting distracted for an hour
or two and doing that so i don't so i
cut that track up completely when i'm
trading the reason i have a ps2 and not
like a ps5 or there's no ps6 but like
ps6 i don't have any of that it's
because
the ps2 is what i had when i was
homeless and then we had to pawn it to
get money to you know move into the
shelter because it cost money movement
each other it was crazy
and then um
once we moved out the show we bought the
ps2 back and all the video games see
over there like smackdown here comes the
pain final fantasy nba libel fight those
are the games i played so when i'm
trading i'm just waiting i like to do
things that make me happy and and this
brings me to a point to where my dad was
alive in my life every single day and
playing those games remind me of
the times i used to be even though i was
homeless or had like a super small room
my dad was alive and i wish she was here
to see it all so like when i'm trading i
will play a video game to make sure that
like i'm still happy so peaceful but i
can't be on instagram can't be on
tickets i can't get the track i just
like to be peaceful 24 7. sorry for your
loss by the way like oh yeah how did
that like did that like help you like
grind harder like how did that impact
your life because that that i could
imagine that's something huge yeah my
dad died at 49 and i was playing
basketball when it happened um it
definitely impacted my life because
i was not expecting it and um his heart
you just had a heart attack and but
nobody was there to like help him so
like he was he was actually
dead for three days and nobody knew well
i i would i would call him every those
theories call him he wouldn't pick up to
the point i told my mom like go check on
him like he wouldn't like but that was
my best friend and my brother's best
friend he would not pick up for three
days
he wouldn't just do that
so she
like got the security police to bust
into his room after three days and he
was dead on the couch and dead for days
they could tell
people said he was dead for day his body
was already cold dead for days
and it threw me for a little it messed
me up but then i came across forex like
two months later
so when they say that like you know a
loss can like turn into something else
so like there's there's always light at
the end of the tunnel there is because
ever since that point i was like okay
i'm gonna make my dad proud like like
big brother wasn't it was one of my
favorite shows growing up but it was my
dad's favorite show that's why i went on
the show but it definitely was my
motivator behind trading behind all my
business behind everything just to make
him proud so it definitely had an effect
on me he still does
i mean shows like that you did anything
that like nothing held you back from
like to get where you want to go you got
me at that point like that that you use
it as a motivation point to like keep
going forward together yeah that's super
crazy bro
no matter what um i look at that to keep
going for i look at where i came from
which is why i'm so passionate about
this industry like a lot of people
the one thing i hate about this industry
is that there's so much back and forth
yeah like and i'm talking about the
leaders i'm talking about with like the
people who either buy our courses or our
boot camps or or our signals or anything
there's so much like
half love you have hate you and it's
like we're all just trying to make sure
y'all are good you know what i mean like
that's all we're trying to do
and um
but no matter what we're going to keep
pushing and we all have different
motivators you know and you know i know
q worked at target i know sean was like
a plumber or something like that conor
mcgregor was a plumber my dad died i was
homeless crazy yeah you were working at
dunkin donuts you said right we all have
different things that push us to where
we want to get to and keep us going and
that was for me that's crazy bro that i
mean that to me is like not not only
that you were homeless but the fact that
where you are now that to me is you know
obviously ultimate motivation um let's
talk a little bit about um your actual
like what do you do now like what makes
you genuinely happy like like like
because i know like
bro this place is quiet like yeah like
very quiet yeah so like like what's your
schedule like because you know one of
your most viral videos is you know the
day in the life of you know life yeah
that video went crazy yeah um
funny how you structure your day it's
kind of exactly how i do it like i have
every 30 minutes to 45 minutes of my day
structured yeah i can structure like a
breath like i would yeah
i have like every minute structure yeah
how do you like is that still the same
or has something changed yeah some of
the things have changed a little bit but
i'll take you through a schedule right
now because obviously my wife is
pregnant so a little bit has changed but
once she goes to sleep whether that's 12
or 12 o'clock in the morning i go to my
office for the rest of night the entire
night i just work so yeah when i put
those like fours guys having breakfast
at like four minutes in the afternoon
i'm like bro what like what i'm up and
active four in the morning like i'll be
in my office um i'll look for a trade
but i'm a swing trader like you said you
are so i'm not people get confused i
don't trade every day like i i my goal
is to trade once or twice a week and
hold it for two three weeks i love swing
trading because like i said in the
beginning like i like to live my life
i'm not trying to be at the church for
eight hours a day like i
i gave the game
eight years of my life of every single
day when people got to understand is
that people grow to have a second love
and a third love and a fourth love and
for me my second third and fourth love
came from the business that i run which
is the actual swag academy um youtube
with the entertainment and the content
i'm not just trading just by myself
that's the only thing that makes me
happy everything makes me happy people
are asking
you know rihanna for an album she gave
music
10 to 15 years of her life now she's
doing savage x fenty she became a
billionaire from savage not from music
lebron became a billionaire from
endorsements not from basketball same
with kobe conor mcgregor had his biggest
payday believe it or not not from that
mayweather fight he got it from selling
um ira the the the whiskey yeah
it's so you have second or third
different love so having different
streams of income so back to my schedule
my schedule was not just looking for
trading setups for nine hours a day so i
became a swing trader so whole set ups
longer hopefully use a bigger lot size
will hold setups longer then i'm
focusing on the business actual academy
what's going on what can i do to make it
better how am i students doing then from
there i go into youtube should i post a
youtube video today youtube hand me
money should i fall back from youtube
should i do something better with
youtube and then i'm looking at i'm
reading a book i read like three hours a
day i'm looking for new ideas on like
what other businesses can i start what
do i have a passion for and then when i
by the time i work out i'll play
basketball early in the morning do a
full i still do my basketball workouts
if i'm d1 still like i know all those
setups and drills come back shower get
in the pool get in the hot tub relax
still peaceful by the time my wife's up
i may take like a three four hour nap
which is my sleep basically eat
breakfast get up and then
just travel the neighborhood go on a
hike with my wife and just chill and
when i'm not home i will travel because
i guess i travel a lot a lot a lot but
actually my schedule would transfer
that's when you say you train like i i
was telling you swagger i'm like yo i'm
gonna take my basketball shoes i'm gonna
ball you up but tagging's a lot smaller
he's a lot taller than i thought i
didn't know you're so tall you google me
it says i'm 5 10. i'm four and a half
like yeah yeah no he's not i'm not five
ten man i don't know if you people no no
i didn't right this guy you know what
i'm saying if you google yeah so i can
see height it says 510 like yeah you're
talking about you know round ten you
open the door i'm like oh [__] right
like that i was not ready for this yeah
um no but that's lit like like you know
personally when it comes to like the
fitness i kind of like been falling off
a little bit off that because just like
i'm tired you get me but you know that
you're still training like a d1 like you
know like if you're playing ball that's
pretty crazy now though no i'm in dorado
okay when i was in los angeles i fell
off for a good year when i was
my year that i made the most money not
now but like
when in 2020 and 2019 was the year i
made the most money in my life at that
time
i was so locked into that i fell off
from fitness i wouldn't i did not work
out worked out maybe once a month so i
understand but once i got to like that
auto and and kind of got away from like
los angeles i went back right because
you're living now like i'm good exactly
what you said earlier like like you
grinded kind of where i am like my
grinding phase and then now you're just
living now you're just doing your thing
and i still want to grind but i don't
want to like i was literally like got to
a point to where like i was neglecting
my wife to the point where like she was
asking me can we spend time together you
know i mean we used to spend time all
the time together now i'm so focused on
money and like we got enough to be good
and i want more i want more to the point
we had to figure things out because
like
i'm grinding what am i grinding for
you're grinding for your your unborn kid
you're going for your generation okay
cool but you got to make time for things
that are important because tai lopez has
something where it's like as a guy who
he knows who is worth five billion
dollars worth more than ty but he's so
big and overweight he can't get out to
enjoy it and he has a short life
expectancy he's supposed to die in his
like 50s or no he's 50 now in the 60s
because he's overweight and it's like
you've got to make sure you take care of
all areas and when i realized that
i go okay i got to take care of my
health again i got to make sure i'm
working out all the money in the world
means nothing to buy like steve jobs
said
or the people who work steve jobs means
nothing if you die tomorrow from a
disease obviously steve jobs had a
disease you can't really control but
like he died he was the richest person
in the graveyard you know so you got to
make sure you take care of everything
talking about bailey how excited are you
bro the girl uh for for my girl yeah so
i have a girl where her name's gonna be
a laura lee i'm excited um it didn't hit
me until we had the gender reveal like
the first four months bailey was
pregnant it didn't hit me just felt like
okay like we just have a kid's coming i
just never knew it until like it was
real
and
i grind for my kids you know even though
i don't have any right now but i like
being homeless my goal was to be the
best father i could be so that my kids
never got to go through what i went
through i don't want them to even sniff
struggle that's why i moved to dorado
that's why she's going to be born here
especially when she's growing grow up
she's all she's going to know is luxury
she's going to have a bentley golf cart
yeah she's going to be lit what i mean
um but that's what what i grind for so
that's why i'm excited because now the
pressure is really on now you really
gotta it's not just umb anymore you
don't brought a kid into this world who
didn't actually come into this world so
now you gotta provide so it makes me
happy that
one i gotta go to a new level
um in my mi whether it's trading game or
business game about my creativity to
provide for her and make sure that she
always keeps the life so that that i
want for her yeah like i said where you
changed your legacy completely like
fully you tell me you're going to bring
out your family here too yeah yeah yeah
so i'll let us out i'm moving my family
out here so the apartments you guys saw
on the tour i'm moving my mom out here
my brother out here and um
a few other people who really means a
lot to me because i want them to
experience this peaceful life because
like
the people close to me are just like me
they're peaceful they don't like
partying too much they don't they be
chilling um
they like to have fun that's why they
they they uh they go out they they go
visit certain places but i've never
drunk or smoke anything a day in my life
i've never tried anything so i like to
just relax and chill but they're all
going to move here i'm moving them all
here and i want my family close to me
and i don't know it'll be perfect yeah i
guess i would like what would you say
out there let's say somebody that you
know maybe let's not say homeless you
know because that's like bro that's
crazy like i i don't want to say like i
can't envision that i've never been in a
position like that like i don't come
from i don't come from poor like i come
from mediocre family like my family it
was very happy with standard they're
very they're they're very happy with
living okay
just being just fine you got me so what
would you you know like what would you
recommend or like what would be like a
piece of advice you could give out to
somebody that's like living okay maybe
under that kind of going through some
struggles what would it be yeah spend
money on on yourself you know like i i
people have an issue with
uh programs and courses or or or
self-development books like you know the
rich man in babylon or the success
principles anything in general spend
money on yourself because that's the
only way you're gonna get out of it by
trying to penny pinch is not gonna i'm
talking about if you're really really
important yes it saves save some money
but i'm talking about like if you have
some money to like spend do not try to
throw it into an account don't try to
you know get into the latest scam like
spend money on yourself in in in
programs because that's the only way
you're gonna get people don't know i
spent money on
eight to nine different courses i've
read over
you know seven hundred eight hundred
books even though i have like
a thousand plus books in my library i
probably read maybe seventy eighty
percent of them it's crazy yeah and you
have to spend money on yourself to learn
these new things you can't just unlearn
like you said about your family you
can't unlearn standard
by walking into it you have to
hear a different perspective listen to
different podcasts read certain books
and open your mind to different things
and for me i had to read all those books
or go through everything i went to buy
all those courses to get to the point i
am today and like i said every course
that i bought played an integral role on
me being here even if i don't trade the
same way like i i started with ty and i
bought steve morrow's beat the market
maker course and i bought jason
stapleton's course she doesn't even
trade anymore and i bought storm uh
storm bryant now storm lewis course no
storm lewis now she got married named
storm bryant i bought her course she was
fire bought somebody else's course
bought asheville's course i bought like
literally eight different courses and
then i ended up making it like figuring
out what i really want to do my own
strategy and and what i love to do
but
i don't look at what there's an issue
with these people that you're talking
about who follow us or follow other
traders they get mad
if they spend money on one course and
it's not the way they like to trade or
or the signals like whoever does signals
doesn't hit for a good month it's like
relax this is a this is a a journey it
took me eight years to get here here i
mean like four years in terms of trading
but like if you go if you even go back
to college like i was homeless at 13
years old it took me years to get here
it didn't come overnight so i would tell
them be patient spend money on yourself
that means books courses podcasts
whatever
and trust the process you're going to
have you're going to have deals that go
bad you're going to have deals that go
good but understand it's a part of the
process i just spent 25 racks even
though i'm in the position right now
it's somebody who's in a better position
to me he does one-on-one mentorship not
in trading but just in
in life in general i just spent 25 racks
for a one-on-one with him for
i think four sessions like what i mean
like i'm still trying to get better
myself and if it doesn't make me better
it is what it is like but i'm not afraid
and that's why people like me and y'all
feel like we're here because we're not
afraid to take risks so please if you're
out there and you're in a bad position
not homeless but in the bad position
take risks and don't fear what happens
on what's on the other side of it have
you taken any risks that you look back
on now you're like damn i low-key regret
it right now there's there's not one
risk that i've taken that i regret i've
dropped out of college
um i i quit tv before i even had like
actual clear clear clear-cut money
um
yeah 14 000 is not money no 14 000. yeah
somebody said 14 000 no no no i i i
there's no risk there's a lot of things
that went wrong like you know what i
mean like hiring certain people who you
know like i think dr drake had a meme
where he said i've taken people who were
in bad positions and elevated them
whether whether i just gave them 50
racks to better better themselves hired
them gave them a better job got them out
of debt i'd done so many different
things different people to where when
they got up they turned their back on me
and did the snakiest stuff and drake
drake said that and that's a meme i not
a meme but a real that i
i feel wholeheartedly but i don't regret
it because it taught me so many lessons
so there's nothing no risks i've taken
that i regret ever talking about uh
people like turn your back on you're
like you know looking back now obviously
you're probably like from your
i don't even want to say you're great
because you don't even probably have
like
a close group of friends because you
didn't you know stay a full year or four
like two three years in high school or
whatever the case is like are there any
of like you know the people from back in
the day like damn you know i didn't
believe in you like now they're like
saying yo what's up everyone yeah
everyone everyone how did i feel
everyone that's why like
when you look at my my gender role
there's only two friends that i i flew
out and brought i would do anything for
them like i i plan on clearing their
debt i haven't done so yet but i plan on
clearing both their debt making flying
them out to experience life with me like
my goal for next year is to go to one
nba game in every single arena and go to
uh
i think all the ufc fights because i
went to ufc event last year it was crazy
in the world yeah i was out with uh
yeah i saw you you took your brother out
there took my brother we sat front row
we met everybody backstage we got in the
ring bro it was a crazy it cost a bag
though but it it
that means more than me than than that
like these chains probably cost me 150
and if i could sell them tomorrow i
would i don't i don't like don't care
about them i wear them out of necessity
like i paid 150 it's here i'm just gonna
wear them i don't like them the ufc
event costs 130 for one for one for two
days 130k 30k for two days for front row
seats to meet dana white talk to them
have dinner with them meet all the meet
the fighters go in the ring
practice the walk to the ring
um
get a private driver to drive you
everywhere have a security guard to walk
you through so when conor mcgregor
people don't know this if you go see
conor mcgregor's ufc 264 walk out me and
my brother was right behind him like we
get to walk out with connor like 130 but
that experience something that means
more to me than any of these chains on
right now um
so back to what you said about friends
yes
but there's only like i can count on one
hand the friends that i will take on
that journey with all the girls out
there there's so many girls out there
who have curd me
coming back in my dms ex-girlfriends um
and
um not ex-girlfriends but like ex-flings
that people i've been with um
teachers people like a lot of people who
didn't people who hated me in high
school are in my dm's like yo you really
made it congrats i'm just like thank you
like
like can we hang can't get you no people
who know me have the audacity to come my
dm is like yo text me here's my number
what i'm gonna text you for i've not
talked to you in eight years why am i
gonna text you there's nothing to talk
about yeah that makes sense going from
homeless to where i am today
like you said i had no role model
whatsoever to look up to so i never
thought about being a billionaire at 14
years old when i like stopped being
homeless and got to like our first like
stable house like a small one two
bedroom i never thought about being a
building i just thought about okay i
want to make enough money to make sure
my family is good so i don't even know i
thought a million dollars a little was a
lot of money
so people out there watching i mean
those there's a lot of money it's not a
lot of money to me it's not not because
that's not like a flex i'm just saying
that like i've gotten to the point where
i'm used to it now and and the things i
want for like my daughter and my wife
cost a lot more than that because of my
future generations but at that point i'm
like okay i want to be a millionaire i
want to be a millionaire i want to be a
millionaire i want a million by 25.
what really set it off to answer your
question really was
at
i just turned 19 years old february 17th
2014.
i had a girlfriend at the time who was
everything to me
um we we dated all through high school
dated for four or five years loved her
family to death and
i mean she was just the world to me and
i found out that she was cheating on me
we went to different colleges i was a
freshman and i found out she was
cheating on me
and
when she cheated on me she blocked me
and i never got a closure or excuse on
why it happened it messed me up like it
completely messed me up
and it wasn't until that happened so i
said i am like my goal literally at that
point was i'm going to make her regret
ever leaving me that is my number one
main goal
in doing that that is when i came across
books financial literacy
because of a stupid breakup which is
crazy and then i get to a point where
i'm rich where i don't care about the
bricker no more but it started because
of that it didn't start because like my
dad died after the breakup you know what
i mean like so that that fueled me even
more but to get to the point where i
didn't have a role model or anything
like that none of that stuff
like i didn't think about the grand
scheme of things until i got cheated on
and then it was like oh i really gotta
figure out how to be
the next whoever in this world and once
that happened i
researched so much and i got to the
point where i am now it started because
of that and i started looking up role
models reading every single book i think
of my dad died motivation things to
happen after that that breakup set it
all off though and to your family now
that you plan to like bring out like how
does like how do they see you because
like you know my family they're latin
like like i told you they they're cuban
they don't really like see understand
anything that i do yeah like they are
still like bro what are you doing yeah
they're clueless right yeah what about
you because like you know you guys are
in the states you know you're from new
york so at least you know maybe um
you know we have access here and stuff
in the states that obviously we don't
have in cuba so like how do your you
know family see it now that where you
are now my family doesn't understand why
i'm here in puerto rico they don't until
they visit like my family's gonna come
and visit in like two or three weeks my
brother came and visited he understands
completely uh one of baby's friends came
to visit she understands but
they don't understand you know my mom is
just happy she's retired like like we
were talking about people getting laid
off during the pandemic my mom got laid
off during the pandemic and she was
crying because she didn't know where
income would come from i told my mom
you're good like i i'll pay all your
bills to retire right now and she's like
are you sure like sure like i don't know
how sustainable what you're doing is all
this extra stuff
and people understand about like me
telling my mom like i'm dropping out of
college you need to support me or not
support me she ended up supporting me i
dropped out so i told her i'm gonna
retire you one day and when she was like
i mean she sent me a video crying her
eyes out saying she just got laid off
and she doesn't know how she's gonna pay
bills and rent this month
at that point i just paid her bills
every month until hey you're retired
don't work again now she's at a point
where she expects things she expects you
know what i mean like oh she expects
vacation she expects you know what i
mean she's you know i'm 51 years old
she's chilling so now she understands
what i'm doing she'll send me
motivational clips on like lebron just
said a billion you're next like she'll
she'll she'll motivate me now because
she understands now but coming up a lot
of family members didn't understand they
didn't understand puerto rico until i
told them like you when you break it
down
like you know first on like first of all
how peaceful it is out here you show
them pictures on videos it doesn't do it
justice until you're actually in here
but then break down the money side on
how much money you could actually save
then it's like oh okay like i i get it
so it takes a while to explain it to
them
sometimes it's better off not explaining
because like i'm my own person i can
live my own life but
um the family will understand eventually
for sure
and then now that like you're here does
it feel real like is it like like has it
hit you yet that you're living here is
it like not hit yet no it hit me it hit
me like i said it hit me that i lived in
dorado uh puerto rico once i went to new
york to go back home and visit my family
in connecticut and i actually hated it i
was like i can't wait to get on the
flight back to san juan and get back out
to puerto rico and i got to puerto rico
and i got chopped off by the the cab to
my doorstep it was like i'm home my pool
my hot tub my office you know we're
still we're still getting acclimated
with the with the environment and still
like we still gotta you know play golf
more and and um i gotta play basketball
more and my office stuff it takes a
little bit longer to get here than it
would in los angeles but it i i live
here bro like it i'm not going nowhere
bro don't trust me i i don't i'm not
trying to leave her i'm trying to
we could go to this podcast for like two
hours i'm not trying to leave it's
beautiful here bro it's a different
element um i'm just thankful for
everybody who's out there who supports
me supports you supports the thing that
we do and
um no matter what
i think we're doing a service to the
community with whatever we're doing i
think if
a lot of people in the industry stay out
of drama and just focus on what they're
doing then a lot of the audience has to
follow suit and kind of go from there
whether it's a prop firm or the signals
or courses or actual trading all of that
benefits every single person i think a
lot of the industry leaders are doing a
good job and i just hope that the fans
or the audience see that we're trying
our best to make sure
you guys are are good because we wanted
to we really could could could sit back
and just focus on ourselves and we do
that sometimes but a lot of times we're
we're doing things for them like doing
launches doing boot camps doing doing in
person classes we're doing that all for
them and i hope they can appreciate that
fully one day that's awesome what would
be one last piece of advice you could
give out there to a startup trader just
anybody like china trying to live in
dorado
trying to live in dorado uh one piece
for starter trader is
is what i said in in the beginning um
don't be afraid to try new things
um try as much as you can do not give
yourself a time limit like people i said
before if you give yourself a time limit
to learn how to trade you're a scam like
you you want to say all these people who
sell courses are scamming your scam you
came in saying i'm gonna i'm gonna
not not like the industry i'm talking
about a random trader who's struggling
you came into this industry thinking
you're gonna make money in a month and
then you don't make money in a month
somebody else's scam no yours you're the
scam because you came in with the wrong
expectations thinking is going to happen
overnight when a lot of us busted our
ass for years to get here and then we
get here yeah we still love trading we
still trade but we're starting new
ventures and it's like oh you're not
helping us as much and no we still are
but
understand that
try things
don't be don't be afraid to take risk
and and stop trying to be handheld into
this industry nobody held our hand to do
things we had to get it out of the mud
we had to take new all these courses
trial and error our biggest losses our
biggest wins in this market we had to go
through the ups and downs the ebbs and
flows of everything
we did it so people out there who's
watching us use us as inspiration
whether it's joining our program joining
signals don't join go baby pips go be on
the stock market do something else but
don't don't give yourself a time limit i
don't care if it takes eight years nine
years ten years people gotta understand
they're looking at everybody out here
all these leaders who are i'm gonna try
to wrap this up i have so much to say
it's just it's just a lot but no go
ahead they they they see somebody making
500 000 in a month trading and they
think that's realistic that is an
anomaly meaning like it can happen but
it's like the best of the best of the
best realistically people don't know
like the stash say if you make over 80
000 a year trading a year you are one of
the best of the best now obviously you
know like there's one there's uh george
soros best and there's warren buffett
best from investing but
somebody making 500 5000 a day or 150
000 a day use that as motivation but
when you don't do it and you're only
making 8 000 a month that is amazing
because you're making a hundred and
something k a year people don't
understand when it came like
it's just it's just so much because you
know there's so many things you can do
and then aside from trading people don't
understand people want to talk about
people who have you know uh programs and
courses i want everybody to to go
research is when this podcast ends and
tell me if i'm lying in the comments
somebody go tell me what was warren
buffett's first job first real job
people don't know this he was selling
courses called investment principles in
nebraska you know where he went to
college before he even made a million
dollars ever investing he was selling
investing a court seminar they called it
back in the day it wasn't a court but a
seminar called investment principles
teaching people how to invest when his
last investment fails i'm not saying
that's that's what everybody does i'm
saying that like
nobody talks about warren buffet they
want to talk about people in this
industry they don't talk about warren
buffett that way because he did that
used that money then used money from his
nine-to-five job combined both money to
finally make his first real investment
and then started going crazy then became
the president of
berkshire hathaway he started and then
he became rich man in the world then
bill gates came to the elon camp then
jeff bezos came but nobody knows that's
how he started so people out there long
story short take risks and do not give
yourself a time limit on how long it
takes to be successful in this market
and just live life that's it like
everybody's trying to help you out here
don't think everybody's out here trying
to be for themselves they're trying to
help you but also be a man be a woman
and take initiative yourself is that
it's almost not even fair like when i
did the meet and greet earlier here in
puerto rico there's like oh bro like
i've been like three months like you
know trading i haven't made any money
and i'm just like we're like why are you
complaining bro like it's all like it's
almost not even fair like i still lose
to this day and i don't complain to
nobody like you've been risking a couple
hundred bucks like pro i
for example like um oh i i took let's
just say anything right like oh i took
your course and i haven't made any money
from it bro dude like you're not doing
the things right you get me like it's
almost not even fair that you just
finished watching the video and the next
trade you take at the end of the video
it doesn't hit the problem it doesn't
yeah yeah like it's not like you're not
even being fair to me that i put up the
risk for what three four years to kind
of figure out where i am now you get me
like i'm putting up these thousand
dollars every single night when i take a
trade like you're not being fair to me
like you're being selfish you got me
kind of just like put ourselves in a bad
situation yeah bro it's a tough
situation because
i can show you several people who have
became profitable for my course and i
could show you several people a lot of
people who just complain and like i've
been in your course like you said five
months i'm not profitable yet and like
keep keep going keep studying it's not
just and what i tell people out there
that it's not just going to be my course
i keep telling people i took nine
different courses and i put things
together and i figured out myself so
take the best piece of advice that you
got from my course then go on youtube
then go buy somebody else's course take
somebody's bootcamp go do this try this
then once you figure out that you think
that you've gotten enough information
and now something to try to put it
together then put it together but
there's a reason like our programs do
not say or signals whatever that hey you
join us you're guaranteed to make money
i was not guaranteed to live in the same
neighborhood as tight lopez from buying
his 67 steps program there's people on
youtube with a million views calling tai
lopez a scam like a million views saying
i hate them
i took a 67 program and mind you it was
and they're complaining about that or
they're complaining about mentor box
where he does um he he has people who
give summaries of books for seven
dollars a month it's the biggest scam in
the world you spent seven dollars you
spent 200 you spent like you didn't even
spend the money keep
going through things because tai changed
my life i live in the same neighborhood
and because of how he gave me the
foundation then i took initiative i
didn't ask ty to hold my hand i didn't
there was millions of people who bought
that course i figured that out went to a
foundation went to reading books and
then i went from there and people out
there just need to take their time stop
saying i've been here for six months and
and i haven't done things you can know
that and take a break there's no wrong
there's no reason there's no nothing
wrong with taking a two week or three
week break and there's a reason and it's
the last thing i'll say because i feel
like there's so much more i can say but
realistically is that there's a reason
where like
a lot of
traders out there
you can't find too many it's hard to
find one who has
my fx book linked for like 10 years
straight reason being is because one a
lot of us are private we keep our
accounts private we keep everything's
private two and i told bayless the other
day you know me was talking about like
you know bank accounts like that i told
you that like back in the day when we
didn't have that much money there's a
reason why i never told you how much
money we were making or losing because
you would freak out so when it comes to
the my effects but one month i may make
20 racks 50 racks 40 racks the next
month i may lose 4 thousand or six
thousand i may have a red month and
four green months in a row then one red
month somebody may come and be like oh
you look like people when you say you're
losing your stories like oh you lose
you're you're supposed to be this master
trader no i'm not i'm a great trader we
still lose we're all human beings like
kobe bryant is one of the greatest
players of all time he also missed the
most shots in nba history by far barry
bonds theme or on the very bottom of
hank aaron the most strikeouts in nba
history also the most home runs in nba
mlb history
it's a it's a real life thing you know
what i mean so i need people to
understand that like you said we still
lose we still do this but we keep things
private we try to teach as much as we
can you will see people like link on my
facebook for like a three-month period a
six-month period a one-year period
anytime somebody even shows you that be
grateful they don't have to show you
that but when they do show you that be
grateful but like people do take breaks
they take a like for me like i remember
i took a a three-month break last year i
traded for nine months i took a
three-month break not consecutively i
took like a one month break back to
trading one month break but
it happens i'm not i don't want to trade
every single day 12 months a day so if
somebody's losing back to the original
question and they're losing for six
months seven months
take a break
like realize what you're doing it for
then come back with a sound mind the
next month and see how that helps you
and i definitely feel like with a lot of
traders like they always ask oh how long
did it take for you to get profit when
it's like we're like my time is
different than yours like for me it took
two two and a half years you're telling
me four yeah q says six months you said
so i'm saying yeah so it's like bro like
everybody's looking for like that answer
like oh all right bet like you know five
months so and two days i'm not
profitable you're a scam you're wrong
you got me that's where a lot of people
kind of have that wrong mindset and
that's that i think is because they
don't want it bad enough they're just
looking for like the time to come and
then like oh someone to to like blame
you get me kind of have like an excuse
right somebody wrote me the other day
and said
quick how can i if i take your course
can i make ten thousand dollars next
month real fast if so i'll buy it right
now i said don't waste my time don't buy
it just don't buy it you're just gonna
set yourself up for failure because you
can't give yourself a time if i told
myself if i never popped off my fourth
year and i was a babysitter my seventh
year in
i would have still kept learning how to
trade i knew it was my my exit point to
get out of what i was doing i wasn't
going to find anything that was better i
wasn't going to find 9 to 5. it was
better stop giving yourself a time limit
and and trust yourself like trust trust
the journals that you're or the books
you're reading have a trading journal do
what you got to do study all of it and
track your trades and stuff but
stop giving yourself a time everything
is different i would love to come in and
learn how to trade for six months but
for me i had to go through those years
of struggle go on a tv show think i was
going to be the next crazy person my
wife put bring me back into shape and
tell me no you're like be back in the
trading
almost drown on national tv to the point
where i'm like all right i'm never doing
this again and to get to the point where
i'm in today it's funny that you said my
job we have a friend that didn't know
how to swim either really [__] with him
all the time bro
yeah it's crazy because like you know
you guys when you guys are like from up
north you guys don't really go like the
beaches or pools
not in connecticut new york exactly yeah
i mean bro you know i'm born in miami
you know you always go to the beach put
that's why i'm laughing but yo swag i
generally appreciate you the gems
bringing me to your crib showing me
dorado like and i'm gonna be honest like
changing
my perspective like my new standard has
just like elevated i swear to god really
like i had a goal and like that is [__]
to me now i swear to god
so i appreciate you i have i have
different i want to go so fast and we
can get out of here like i have a
um
i have a a 3 million
trading goal this year like that that's
my goal for trading profit profit yeah
the three million dollars in my trading
i said 1.73 like that's my goal people
got like that that is my trading goal
business-wise i would love to make
not just like i include youtube cause
youtube was paying me 40 50 racks a
month at one point when i was being
consistent i would love to
you know make six to 10 million with all
the businesses that i do and all the
investing i do and hopefully bring in
you know anywhere between 10 to 15 next
year like that those are my goals um but
like i said i hope it's a standard for
people watching i have different goals
have a trading goal have a business goal
a nine to five goal if you haven't have
different goals don't just put all your
eggs in this one trading basket put in
that basket and then do the others as
well
so that's it
yo appreciate you like yo thank you for
coming live
take it easy guys